# MD. FAYZULLAH AMAN

WEB DEVELOPER



## **CONTACT**

- ☑ fayzullahaman@gmail.com
- \$\square\$ 01795504043 \/ 01916955766
- (p) Uttor Badda, Dhaka, Bangladesh
- 😚 fayzullahaman.bdprogrammers.com
- in linkedin.com/in/fayzullahaman
- github.com/fayzullahaman

# **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap	
JavaScript, jQuery	
PHP, MySQL	_
WordPress	
Angular	
React	
CodeIgniter	_
Laravel	_
Vue	

## ABOUT ME

Assalamu Alaikum

Nice to meet you! I have 5 years of experience as computer operator. Recently I completed web development course from IsDB-BISEW and gained experience in web development. Now I am working in web design and development. Languages I know are HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Jquery, PHP, MySQL, WordPress, Angular, React, CodeIgniter, Laravel and Vue. I am very interested in sharing my skills in web development to the public. My passion is creating and developing a professional, beautiful website. I am committed to maintain a professional relationship with my clients and provide efficient and reliable service according to their needs. Contact me now to discuss your next project.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

**Computer Operator** 

The Royal Scientific Publications 2018 - 2022

**Data Entry Operator** 

Golden Harvest InfoTech Ltd. 2017 - 2018

**Data Entry Operator** 

Computer Graphics & Design Ltd. 2016 - 2017

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Masters**

Al-Hadith & islamic Studies Islamic University 2016-2017

### **Honours**

Al-Hadith & islamic Studies Islamic University 2012-2016

## **HSC/Alim**

Humanities Khamar Bari Nesaria Fazil Madrasah 2012

### SSC/Dakhil

Science

Darunnazat Siddikia Kamil Madrasah 2010